...air-flow patterns and dispersion
of sunlight to make an informed choice.
Why don't you pick at random, if you
don't like it, sit somewhere else next time?
(Sheldon:)No, no, that's crazy.
(Sheldon:)You go ahead and talk
while I figure it out.
(Sheldon:)Okay.
(Penny:)Here's the thing.
(Penny:)So I've known for a while now
that Leonard has had a little crush on me...
(Sheldon:)A little crush?
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose so.
(Sheldon:)In the same way Menelaus
had a little crush on Helen of Troy.
(Penny:)I don't really know who they are...
(Sheldon:)- Menelaus was the brother of Agamemnon...
- Yeah, I don't care. Listen.
(Penny:)The point is...
(Penny:)...Leonard isn't the kind of guy
I usually go out with.
(Penny:)Leonard isn't the kind of guy
anyone usually goes out with.
(Sheldon:)Would you be open
to rotating the couch clockwise 30 degrees?
(Penny:)No. What I'm saying is,
Leonard might be different in a good way.
And obviously, my usual choices
have not worked out so well.
Your last one worked out well
for Koothrappali. He got a free iPod.